Oh, I sold it.
It's okay. It's so good, bro. It's so
free, bro. Oh my god.
>> How much How much is this going to go
up?
>> Oh my god. Oh my I should Bro, I should
have bought way more.
Oh my god.
Oh.
Wait, I'm saved.
And if
I bought the run with the right ticker
based off a new pair.
>> [music]
>> So, I just saw here. Ticker is Kishu.
Hopefully
I just bought a little half the port,
but I think this fam's this though. I'm
way around trip. Got a really good
entry. And okay, I'm saved a bit. How is
this not vamping, bro? This is the
[music] ticker, guys. Should I just take
the 0.1 profit? That might be the method
here. I mean, the move right here.
Unless wait, hold on. Other one is
falling. I have a 9K interest, so I'm
going to do this a bit. There we go.
This one dumped. Oh my god, we are paid,
bro. We are paid like three. There we
go. This one is just a zero. Is that it?
That's the top? I guess that is the top.
I'll take this, bro. Whatever. I'll take
the 0.1. Damn, we were up like 0.3, no?
That's crazy.
Just knowing what's running can make you
so much money, all right? [music] So, I
found this Louie coin that's running
already at 100K market cap, but I see
Louie the duck, and I see a dog in that
video, right? And I didn't see any dogs
like coins running yet. So, this is at
100K, so I was just expecting the coin
to be like, I don't know, hopefully 5K,
and I was right. So, this Louie coin is
just running so hard, and people are
spamming on new pairs Barley the dog.
Look, as you guys can see, I saw it. So,
I'm just going to type in Barley, see if
there's an OG. I misspelled it right
here. Once again, I'm doing this on
undoxed wallet, the first one to 10 sol.
You got to buy 0.5. Remember, it's in
the Barley D here. Reason why I'm buying
some Barley is because [music]
this is a miracle duck, right? And uh uh
and uh miracle duck and Barley is the
perfect derivative. Okay, yeah, we're
paid. Oh my god, I'm actually so smart.
And this is the duck and this is the
dog. So I just bought the dog at $4,000
market cap. If I bought this with my
main wallet, probably would have bonded
but I guess you got to hold a bit. And
this is waking. While this wakes, we can
chill on the dog. Worst case scenario is
just break even. Oh my god, bro. It's
just that easy to make meme coins, bro.
Now this bonds, we made like three sol.
It's pretty good for our portfolio. All
I did was just scan, bro. I didn't even
buy anything. I'm just looking at these
like narratives. Hopefully it does bond.
[music] Hopefully this goes like 300k
and if this goes like 100k, god, we're
so paid. Now I could scale 20 bucks but
I really do believe in the narrative.
[music] This is just a all-time high.
Probably just going to be like the riff,
I guess. Just got to chill, I guess.
I'll just take this profit. Okay.
Hopefully I don't regret that decision.
[music] It probably does bond but it's
all good. We made profit. Profit is
profit. I just booked. So that's sold
[music] twice. Refresh the page. Yeah,
whatever. Made 84 bucks. I then decide
to rebuy just because the Louie, the dog
is ripping and they just paid decks.
Yeah, I'll let you get in here [music]
cuz they just paid decks. Look, it's
pending right here. Louie just went
crazy. Yeah.
The dog and the duck, bro.
What is going on, bro? I don't
Oh, [snorts] that's disgusting.
People are just impatient, bro. There we
go. Just Just bond this. The dog is as
free as the duck. I just sell.
Maybe it sells without me if I just sell
right now.
I will hold. The dog is getting a lot of
volume.
Wish I hadn't sold down there. Yeah,
like two [music] here. Actually I feel
like I feel like I did well with my
sells. I'm going to take 50% here just
to secure some P. [music] So I can It's
okay higher. Duck and the dog. Check if
there's anything else to buy.
Mantis. Oh hell no, I don't want watch
this. Ain't no Ain't no no.
There we go. Just feels so good to be
This is This is the rewarding about meme
coins. Just being right, bro. Even if it
means holding a bit. I'll take another
50% here. [music] My god, what a sell
for me. Did I get 24K? What? Did I get
24K, bro? Whatever. Oh my god, it's just
going crazy. Bro, I literally had Look
at this entry, my initial entry, just
because
Now it's just going up. I'd rather buy a
coin at the bottom and risk losing like
0.1 max to try to make like one or two
sol, rather than buying a coin up here
trying to scalp it, bro. Should bond,
no? The volume is getting I might sell
right before bonding.
Oh, no.
29? Okay, 29 is not that bad. Just made
an extra sol, I think, which I will
happily take. Bang, bro. We are now at
three solana tokens just because [music]
of being right.
Now no one shilled me this coin. I found
this coin purely on my own. What
happened to the chart? Oh, did bond,
yeah.
Wow, I had 0.5K initial entry. Now it's
just going to get None up None up None
up. Honestly, bro, we will take that.
[music] I don't care if this goes a
million-dollar market cap, I just made
some money. Just made 145 bucks. [music]
He then found a coin called I won't say
it just because
I'm I don't know what's YouTube's
policies. Well, basically, there was
another coin at 2 million with cashback,
[music] but this one is by the original
creator himself saying, "Oh, he's the
first one to ever post about the meme,
and he's the origin creator." And I
found that $5,000 market cap by just
tracking wallets. I tracked the wallet
named Earl, and he has the CA in his
bio, and it's this coin. [music] And
yeah, I bought in literally the perfect
entry. And I'm not going to lie, bro,
buying on an undoxed wallet is like
crazy. So, here I just like compare the
market cap [music] evaluation that's at
2 million, and this one is at the only
$3,000 market cap. Like, wait, why is
[music] this kind of cheap? You know, at
the most I could lose is 0.1, 0.2. So, I
was like, all right, let me just buy it
and hold. I only put in a soul anyways.
It's not much, but I can make a lot if
it does bond. Yeah,
>> [music]
>> we're just going to hold and wait.
All right, so I sold just because
[music] he promoted a different coin 5
hours ago. It's not good.
Oh, I guess they just needed [music] my
sell. My god, I sold and it's just going
up, bro. That's really unfortunate. Uh,
welcome to the story of my life.
Shamelessly so unfortunate that I
[music] literally sold the dead bottom
and the coin literally migrates, bro. It
bonds and it goes like 70K back to 20K
back to 500K. Bro, that's I don't know.
That's so unlucky, bro. Honestly, this
is why I love using terminal or Padre,
whatever you guys want to call it,
because look at this. A new coin spawns
in. I look at it. It's a really good
narrative. It's getting a lot of volume,
right? And I was about to buy. Don't get
me wrong. Until I look, I scroll down
and there's an OG with already DEX paid,
so I just buy and I'm already up, bro.
Boom. It's just that simple, bro. Make
sure you guys use first link in the
description. You guys support me, bro.
You guys get 35% cash back. It's the
best platform. It's better than any
other competing platform, which only
gives you 25%. This platform gives you
35%. [music]
Bro, you don't Bro, this is the fifth
time. Bro,
no, bro.
No. Oh my god. As you guys could tell, I
was pretty devastated, bro. Like,
imagine selling and the coin just wicks
up. And not only that, whenever I hold a
coin, I just round trip it, bro. Like, I
don't even sell. I sell for a loss. And
that's happened so many times in this
video, bro. It's devastating. You guys
are going to keep watching the video and
you guys are going to see. I just sell
and then boom, wicks, and bonds. You
know, as I'm scanning, you know, I I
just exited a trade in minus. See a coin
here getting some volume once again with
the filters that I've shown you guys at
the beginning of the video. You know,
cops he bought it, he sold though. So,
here I'm just doing my research. I go to
the pump one app, see if there's a
description. Okay, there's nothing. I'm
checking the brown brown profile who
deployed it. I don't see anything odd
here. Like, why is this getting bids?
Why is this getting volume? I'm like,
okay, this is weird.
Maybe the image is something. I don't
know. And then I see the dev still has
like some supply. It's pretty bundled. I
check the dev dev wallet on Twitter
using Padre once again, first
inscription, 35% cashback, nothing
suspicious. And then I see he just sent
supply out. Uh, I don't know if you guys
saw that, but his dev supply, he
literally just sent it out. And I'm
like, what? I go back and the coin is
pumping. I'm like, okay, what's this?
It's pumping. And then I notice, oh
yeah, he did send supply out to someone.
If you guys check the holder list,
there's like a insider icon. I go to
copy that, go to x.com, that's where
usually all info. And then I see, oh,
Pintoshi. Who is this guy?
I buy some.
I buy I I basically full port. I check
for more wallet, see how much followers
he has see how much money he has see how
much followers he has. And he has
900,000 followers and they just sent
supply to this guy. So, I'm like, this
is pretty good. He basically has some
motion. And then one of the wallets I'm
tracking buys in. That's a pretty good
indicator. This guy is pretty good
wallet. If you see him buying on top of
you, that's pretty good. That means
you're early. Trying to buy a signal and
it works. We bought a bond. Bang. As you
guys can see, we're ripping now. We're
just chilling. And oh my god, I should
have taken profit. But I I still like
the coin.
I bought I think a little bit more. Just
try to give it some volume. Once again,
I'm I'm I'm on on docs wallets. So, no
one knows if I'm bad signaling. I'm just
trying to give it volume. You guys don't
know the volume bot method. Just a point
one. Here we start going up. I think
people are starting to realize the
narrative. Well, you guys know me, just
compound your wins, stack up. You guys
know how like similar similar similarly
you guys grind down your port and they
redepot and then over time you lose 10K.
It's similar similar to how you guys
make take profit and make 10K by taking
small wins.
So, we're just going to take profit,
bang, and we're out. Let's go to the
next coin. I'm going to have to voice
over this part just because background
noises. Anyways, so I see this coin
getting bought up by a dev wallet that I
am tracking. This guy is a good dev. He
doesn't like, you know, rug pull. He
does what he says in his tweets, which
is, I think, sending supply out to
wallets. And APU is like a derivative of
Pepe and they this FOMO always
posts APU. And yeah, basically, I'm just
waiting for entry. I'm doing my due
diligence. I'm doing research in it. You
know, it just like it spawned at 25K. He
has 40. The dev sells 39%, but he said
he's sending supply out and that's
pretty good. Not always though, depends.
And here I'm just looking at like old
coins. There's one 9 minutes old at 40K.
And then I'm like, "Wait, if this one's
at 40 or like 40K and then this one."
I'm just making sure that like there's
no OG.
And I do check the search bar and there
is an OG at 200K and it's pretty [music]
active as well, as you guys can see. But
I think just because of the volume how
much volume we were getting at the
start, it was like worth the risk. I
would have had like risk management and
sold worst worst case scenario sold
break [music] even. But I still wanted
to like gamble on this. Like it's I
don't know how to explain it, bro. It's
[music] like intuition. I don't know.
Pattern recognition, probably. That's
the word right word [music] for it. So,
I just buy here at 50K to sell. This
coin I I believe went to a a mill or 2
mill later on. But here you guys know
I'm just I'm to take scalps. Start
wicking. [music]
Cut the scented is trying to flood by
spamming sell, but it doesn't matter. If
the coin narrative is good, it'll go.
Here we're just chilling till he sends
out supply. [music] I mean, yeah. You
just chill.
Do my 0.25 bad signal. So, [music] we
get some volume bots buying up the dip.
And then scented rebuys. Let's go. We're
up one soul here. We're up two.
And then at this point I'm I'm thinking
like maybe I should just take [music]
profits here. Cuz we we are basically
just scalping it, bro. We're up 70, 80%
[music] take some clips so it won't
round trip into a loss. Hopefully. Bang.
I notice I got to be faster with taking
profits.
I take so long, bro.
Bang. Close it 25% 25% and then just
keeping tabs open making sure I don't
miss anything.
25%.
Oh, it's so rewarding being right.
Making money. And then we just take We
still made 1.6 which is not bad. We'll
take that any day of the week. And then
literally right after see a coin bonds
and we just get volume vamped. I'm like,
okay, what is this? Pipo. And I see one
of the tracked wallets
I'm tracking bought something [music]
and it's just getting like I don't know
how to say like dumped you can say. So,
I just watch, you know, waiting for
entry. I'm like, all right, let's let me
try this. And I'm instantly down one so
I'm like, oh my god, what's going on?
So, basically what the narrative was is
this tracked wallet has like a lot of
motion cuz he bought something and it's
like a Pepe narrative like a frog. It's
an animal. So, I guess a lot of
speculation thinking this is something
good. And once again, we got in and dip.
I don't like top lasting just wait for a
dip unless, you know, it's really good
narrative. Seen a lot of people trim
here make me like made me scared so I
just took my profits right around
somewhere here.
Yeah.
I was just like, this is pretty risky.
I'm just going to take the scalp on one
soul. Once again, we're just scalping.
We're just taking one soul P and just
moving on. It's a pretty crowded trade,
in my opinion. A lot of people are in.
That's not like if a lot of tracked
wallets are in, you could say it's like
topped, cuz it's like trenching wallets,
you know? And then the main coin kind of
nuked, the one he was pushing at $12
million market cap. So, yeah, I just
took took my profit and just went on to
the next. You guys remember when I said
earlier there was like a Pepe coin
that's at $12 million market cap. Well,
there's a guy that actually made like a
tweet on it, but he didn't get paid for
it and he's like tweeting that, "Oh, I
want to get like" He's not indirectly
saying, "Oh, I want to get paid." But,
you guys get what I'm trying to say.
>> [music]
>> He's basically like asking for money.
Anyways, here I'm just waiting for the
right narrative. I did bid this one just
in case, because they have supply sent
to him. They're sending fees to the guy
that made the tweet. And the main coin's
at $20 million mark like $20 million
market cap. So, here I'm just looking at
the tweet. He's like, "I inspired the
run of the day. What's Pump Fun doing?
Missed 400X. GG." And he's the one that
made the original tweet before the
original coin that went to $20 million
market cap went. And they're just
sending fees to him just to like
appreciate him, I guess. I got in at
floor. Once again, nothing to lose if
you're buying if you're buying something
at the floor. Here we're just down on my
I'm like I might sell. But, he's pretty
active, so I was like, "Uh, worst case
scenario, we lose like a soul." Once
again, just trying to have some risk
management, especially with the small
port. We're just being patient,
honestly. Hoping he interacts with the
coin within like 10 minutes or
something. Here's the tweet. If you guys
want to pause the video
and go back, read it. [music]
Checking replies. I here I just DM him.
Trying to use a bit of my emotion.
If you guys can see my X DMs, as well.
Oh my god, why is this ripping?
>> Which one?
>> The toad.
>> What?
>> Oh, yeah, he replied.
>> What did he say?
>> Is this real?
>> What did he reply on Twitter reply?
>> 20 seconds ago. Oh my god.
>> What did he say?
>> He said is it real?
>> So I'm replying.
>> Should I like a 100k, no? I don't know.
>> Yeah, this could go higher, I think.
>> Oh my god, it's at 80.
>> Oh my god.
>> What? Tops at 80?
>> Them dude just bought another
>> coin.
>> Really?
>> Sad [__]
>> Oh my god, he sold half.
>> I mean like dude, this is just so
boring, bro.
>> Oh my god, he sold.
>> Yeah, he's a he's I think he's poor.
>> Yeah, I'm out, bro. Whatever. Now that
I've made 10 sol on an index wallet, I'm
back to my main wallet and you know,
[music] we're just scalping. I didn't I
didn't really show the clips of me just
scalping one or two sol, three sol.
>> [music]
>> We found this on new pairs, we're like
all right, let's quick buy this. This is
a pretty good narrative. You see all how
fast I skimmed it? I'm basically saying
new pairs is the way I've made most of
my money and I feel like you guys would
too. Narrative was some guy with the
Pepe mask and this is pretty vi like a
lot of people like to buy stuff like
this. Just like if it's like a meme,
someone's supporting like a meme and
it's like basically speculation that
it's going to go viral. He's robbing
seven stores. So here, we just buy a lot
of it at the bottom and now I'm using my
main wallet to like that signal just so
I can get some motion and we're up seven
sol already, bro.
So then I started doing some research
just to make sure everything's legit,
this news source is legit. You guys have
to be aware of bad actors in the space,
scammers. There's a lot in this space,
especially when money's involved. You
know, I'm trying to like
Here now I'm like sure it's kind of fake
because why else would it move like
that? So we just take our 2.6 sol profit
and move on to the next. Cuz I did
research like through AI, made like I
asked Grok is this real And it turns out
to be fake. Not even 5 minutes later,
we're still scanning new pairs. As you
guys can see, we're just chilling,
listening to some music, and uh we're
just looking at the charts. We're
waiting for anything new to come out.
Hope you guys are having a good day.
And this pops up. Ash. Saw a lot of
volume on it, so it's probably just the
dev sniping it. But, as long as it's
good, it's pretty new. It's an owl.
Yeah, I'm just making sure it's a good
narrative. We direction fees. Okay, so
there's a charity on it. At first, like,
okay, like maybe cash [music] back goes.
So, I buy a lot of the supply, and then
I split it. But, no, I just get rugged.
So, I'm like, okay, I'm just going to
take the loss on this one. So, loss. And
I was like, okay, I guess we have to buy
the main one if you want to buy it, like
[clears throat]
>> [music]
>> this narrative. So, we buy it around, I
believe around here. Just making sure
there's no like vamps. And we just buy
the narrative. Then, we just hold it.
I bought it.
>> [music]
>> It turned out to be faucet.
No.
It's going. Bro.
So, this Trump Pepe?
My god.
This is going to get This is going to
get crimed. 100%.
No. There's another one bonding. Trump
Pepe.
>> This is a faucet, I think, [music]
genuinely.
>> I'm telling you, bro. This is not normal
ball.
>> This is a faucet coin, I think.
>> Pepe or [music]
Which one? I don't know which one.
>> Pepe?
>> I don't know. We start buying up here
and then it just goes like half a mil,
probably. Oh, wait. This is faucet. This
is faucet. This is faucet.
They are.
>> Yeah. Look too. Oh my god. This guy has
2%.
>> Flames is up as well.
Anything bonding is just ripping. Oh my
god. The thing is I saw this and I just
didn't like think [music] much of it.
>> This guy is former candidate for US
Congress, army with veteran.
>> Is he actually Oh my [music] god. That's
so good. He just round tripped.
>> he he he he he he He's selling. He's
selling. He's selling.
He sold one wallet. Not Not everything,
though. Oh, he's he's he's taking P now,
yeah.
>> Yeah. Well, I'm in now.
>> Good. Send it higher now.
>> It's so good.
>> has like 2%, but that
>> Yeah. 2% is nothing, yeah. Faucet. This
faucet. Faucet. Faucet. Wait, let me
call this on the app. Let me call this
on the app. Hold on. Here we are. I got
some motion on.
>> Let's pump.
>> Follow it.
Tegs plus me plus Trump plus Pepe
wanted.
I called it. Let's see.
>> if you can see that, but
>> Oh. Oh, the faucet. The faucet.
>> [laughter]
>> Oh, what?
>> How much did he just buy? What the hell?
>> I was trying to bad signal. I guess he
got me.
>> No, he's just topping. Yeah. Yeah. I
think this goes so much higher.
>> I'm going to take some P, though.
>> Oh my god. Oh my god.
>> god. That wasn't even me. That wasn't
even I only took eight sold, bro.
>> I I think I swear it was higher. I don't
know why we're selling here. But, I I I
have been round trip for lately, so I
don't know.
>> Exactly. Like, I don't know. This is so
good, though. This is so good.
>> Yeah, but I mean, beans buying up here
is kind of a good sign. I can't lie.
>> Yeah. What's true? 200k?
>> Zero? How much?
>> 200. Yo, the faucet is out.
>> Is it out?
>> god.
>> Oh my god. No.
>> No.
No.
What?
>> We just don't care anymore? Yeah, so I
guess you're right. You sold the D top.
Wow.
>> Yeah, but I barely got anything out.
It's just initials, bro. Wow, bro.
>> Yeah, that's better than me. I I took
nothing.
>> I only made 10. It was like like 30,
bro. Rip. This part of the video I kind
of have to explain what's going on. So,
basically, there's a competition versus
a FOMO and pump fun tweet that came out
out of like a news Twitter account. And
there's a bunch of Remus's account like
coins on my graded tab right now. And
basically, we're just trying to find
like a the perfect narrative to send for
this. And that's exactly what we do. So,
right here, we're just waiting for the
right one to kind of come up. And one
just spawns.
I have to start blasting this one
because I feel like this is the this is
the OG, 4 months old. And it says
official FOMO mascot. This is literally
a mascot of the FOMO app. And it's
Remus, which is said by the founder of
the FOMO app. So, I just start blasting.
I blasted 20 so that's the profits
almost half the profits of the day.
>> Oh, I sold it.
>> What the [__]
>> It's okay.
>> It's so good, bro. This is so free, bro.
Oh my god.
>> How much How much is this guy up?
Someone has to pay.
>> I don't like this 80%er.
I don't like this 80%er, bro.
>> 80%er? No, forget that.
>> Someone has 80%.
>> No, what?
>> Look at it. Look at top holders. It's
all the same person.
>> Oh my god. Oh my bro, I should have
bought way more.
Oh my god. Just send this one, guys.
What?
30 minutes older, by the way. 30 minutes
older.
>> Oh my
>> Wait, Thomas Steft? It's Elon, though.
It's Elon. It's Elon.
>> What?
>> Oh my god.
Pump life is good.
>> I love
>> It's Elon though.
>> I'm going to buy them with the other
one, too, the one that's not dancing
there just in case cuz I swear people
hate that guy.
>> I'm going to have to buy a new pair.
Bro, on my
>> Oh my god, anyway, I'm lucky it just up.
I'm at 30, yeah.
>> This is This is so good. This is so
good. This is so good. It's the best
coin ever. I'm not throwing.
>> Pump life is like the best token ever.
>> I don't give a [__] I'm drawing, bro.
I'm tired of losing. I'm at 30.
>> I I just buy here?
>> Oh my god, dude. All right, please send
the vamp one. Please send the vamp one
since they hate Ansem dev. Please
>> Oh my god, cops here. Cops here.
>> I'm unlucky.
>> Oh, bro, I'll send this one though.
>> I let past trades affect future trades.
>> Oh, this is so good. Oh my god, bro, and
uh
Yeah, a good one, bro, and I don't know
why Elon has it.
>> Why is that Why is Elon here?
>> I mean, I guess it's better cuz people
are like less scared of it.
>> I guess, yeah. I guess Elon is better.
>> Black.
>> Yeah.
>> Black. I sold early.
>> Welcome to the club, bro.
>> This is the worst feeling. I'd rather
lose all my money. I've got another
round trip. I need I need something to
happen to this chart so I can buy,
please.
>> 100, bro. I would've been up 80 there.
[__] me.
>> Oh, it's low-key cuz the whole narrative
is the other one.
>> Wait, what's this one? It's Jun Tao.
>> I'm at
>> I mean, I swear it's better. What?
>> So, they're at 100K, bro.
Oh my god,
>> What am I doing? What am I doing? It's
so good, bro. Why am I not buying none
of them? What am I doing?
>> Dude, pump life is actually Jenny.
>> Yeah, bro, what? That was so free.
>> God, money, family, bro.
>> Yes, I'm telling you.
>> I think it goes so high.
>> And if like Jun Tao runs it, goes like
mills, bro.
>> Well, he Are you talking about the other
one?
>> I mean, yeah. I mean, Elon's never going
to support the coin, obviously.
>> Yeah, but you actually
>> Yeah, until he does the call out.
>> [laughter]
>> I don't know.
>> Pulls out his [__]
Pops his old one on the coin.
Going to be a
It's going to be a real sticky situation
when he pops the hole. My god, I don't
know why. Why did I sell it down there?
I let past trades affect future ones.
[music] Gee [__] gee. Wow, bro.
>> Whatever. Give me that.
>> Just holy vaping. It's just God, this is
the main one now.
Like I think it's going to have a fud
dip either way. Like when when there's a
picture, no way just
>> No, no, no. It won't.
>> My god, you're right. Yeah.
>> They're just going to rip the decks.
>> forever.
>> So I do need to explain this narrative.
So basically, Elon Musk just made a
brand new account on Twitter and called
it bot. He got the handle literally just
bot and it has the SpaceX
affiliation badge on it and it's
speculation that's going to be like Grok
and Grok went so high on SOL, I think 30
mil and then Gork went 100 mil on SOL.
So basically, just speculation thinking
that this is pretty good and this isn't
even on SOL right now. This is BNB and I
wouldn't suggest trading on other chains
unless you guys are are profitable on
SOL and have decent knowledge on what's
going on. So this is just me This is
just an extra clip of me round tripping
10K, I believe. 20 BNB. I was up 20 BNB
at the top or you guys are about to see.
>> [music]
>> on SOL right now.
>> Right. Oh my god, bro. I'm up
>> I'm up 10, bro.
>> Oh my god, bro.
>> I just got the
Oh my god. I just got the craziest fill
ever. What the [__]
>> Why did we not take P, Omar?
>> Because it's a
>> Danny's actually smart. Why were you not
listening to Danny?
>> no, I mean
Bro, it's just him selling. People are
people are worried now. Like I still
think it's good, but I just don't know
how long I got to hold on.
>> Yeah, I mean it's just catalyst based as
Stuke said.
>> Either could be like I heard on
>> Yeah, I'm out, bro.
>> happened?
>> I'm out.
>> I can't one clip. I [music] will send it
to you if I want to. Oh my god. Oh my
god, I'm down so much money.
>> What's up, everybody? I wanted to go
through my filters and my settings and
the best platform to be trading on all
in like within my hopefully 2 minutes.
And I would highly suggest you guys
watch this because this is how you guys
are going to set up your whole platform,
your whole trading system, or your
trading however you guys want to trade,
right? So, first of all, we are trading
on trade.proj.dg.
It'll be first link in description and I
will I won't lie, it is my referral
link, but it does support me and it does
help you guys by giving you guys 35%
cashback on all trades. Basically, if we
go to my rewards right here, as you guys
can see, I've made over 400 Solana just
by trading meme coins and that's only
cashback. There's also cashback coins on
coins where there are cashback. As you
guys can see, I still I don't know why I
don't claim these. I just like to save
them up. I still have 11 SOL unclaimed
here, but that's besides the point. Once
again, it's backed by Pump Fun, the
protocol you guys are trading on, and it
has fast fills and it's less laggy.
There are like different servers. For
example, if you guys are in Europe,
there's if you guys are in America, you
know, it's all designated servers. And
I'm going about to go through my filters
and my settings so you guys can have the
same setup as me. And I'm going to give
you guys a tip on Microsoft Edge or on
also on Google Chrome, there is this
setting. I know I'm stuttering a lot,
but so first of all, once again, first
link in description for
terminal/trade.proj.dg,
35% cashback. All right.
>> [laughter]
>> That was a crazy soft shill. Anyways, so
first of all, once you guys are in this
website, you know, you guys deposit
Solana, connect your Phantom wallet,
whatever.
>> [music]
>> You have Solana in the wallet right
here. And first of all, you guys go to
the Trenches tab, you know, there's
trending. [music] Go to Trenches tab and
New Pairs filters, this is what I have.
So, if you go to Protocols, this is what
I have. Moon it heaven, Jupiter, [music]
just play it play back the video if you
guys need to. Mayhem mode, hide, show,
show, and then these. Audit, nothing
here. Metrics, [music] nothing here on
the New Pairs filters. And if you go to
Soon, which is here, right? Everything,
I have dynamic here. Pause the video if
you guys need to. I'll probably will
like speed this I won't speed it up, but
I'm just going to go through it real
quick.
Token H 15 minutes is really important
[music]
on the soon tab. Metrics, we only have
total 0.5 SOL minimum, $6,000 market cap
minimum. And then migrated, I do have
migrated filters now, which is market
cap minimum $100, two total fees, two
Solana, protocols, all this, high
chocho. Now, those are the filters that
I have for me trading. If you go to
customize, uh I'm going to go through
this quickly. Background, I have this on
black, the pump one. Default, it's going
to be green, but I would highly suggest
making this black, and then make bag
screen. You guys can copy these colors.
It's really good. [music]
Avatar,
metrics, I don't think there's anything
here. Metrics, if you got I think people
mess around with this. If you guys want
to change this, but I this is what I
have for metrics. 150,000, [music]
30,000, 1,000. Vitals, I don't think I
have anything here except Yeah, audit.
>> [music]
>> Uh everything's in progress. It's a
ring. Links, I don't think I've messed
with anything here. Address, yeah,
there's nothing [music] here. Let me see
general. Okay, general, this is what I
have on general. Up the trenches
setting, spaced, market cap, bang, bang,
bang on key hold. And then X [music]
preview key is space. So, what this does
is instead of, you know, going covering
over this, I just click space or hold
space, and then it pops up without me
hovering over the tweet link. We go
[music] here, this is my color theme,
Padre font, chart. I have average fill.
I would keep this on probably for you
guys, but I have it turned off [music]
just to know you guys's average exit.
Trading, I don't think I have anything
here. I'll go through my fees in in
[music] a second. Notifications, I don't
like notifications. And then we have our
fees here. So, I have 0.001, 0.001. This
is my trading [music] fees, and uh I
have 0.0004,
four zeros, and then a one, three zeros,
and then a one for the second one. It's
basically [music] so, the more you put
in, you know, the higher the fees you
guys put in, the faster you guys get in,
something like that. Where is the Did I
show the quick buy settings? [music] Oh,
here, quick buy settings. So, width is
max, ultra size, show order on press. On
press is faster, by the way.
>> [music]
>> Main button. Uh this doesn't
Uh yeah, this isn't important. I think
I've gone through everything.
>> [music]
>> And if you guys go click on a chart,
this is my chart. People ask me how to
bring up this, it's right here, instant
trade.
All right?
>> [music]
>> So, this brings up this and you guys can
go ahead and click edit button values
and you guys can copy my values right
here. And I would suggest these values.
And if you guys want to bring it out or
like [music] make it less buttons or
more buttons, you just stretch it out.
And display, this is my display.
I have market cap. I do have indicator,
which is high and low.
And to get this, you just go right click
on here, on any of chart,
go to settings,
and scroll down.
High low, make it value.
You can also put line, but value is the
best, in my opinion. So, you guys don't
get confused [music]
and yeah, that's it. I think that's
everything. Let me just double check. Oh
yeah, I did forget to mention a secret
that not many people know is I just have
to put this on full screen real quick.
Okay, you guys should be able to see
everything, hopefully. So, if you guys
are on Google Chrome or you guys are on
Microsoft, it doesn't matter, right? And
if you guys don't have this in your
browser, then I would highly suggest
switching your browser. Is if you guys
go into the settings in your browser and
you guys go down to system and
performance, and then I believe it's
system. No, it's not system, it's going
to be performance. And I would highly
This is recommended, right? Is you guys
have this turned on. Now, I use
Microsoft Edge because there is this and
there is on Google Chrome for sure, but
this preloads pages for faster browsing
and searching. So, basically, if I go
here on any coin and I click trenches,
look how fast I'm back at the trenches
tab. That is so important, especially
when you guys are playing a game with
money involved. This is so fast, and I
would highly suggest it. And also, I did
forget to mention one thing, micro my
Microsoft Edge is zoomed 110%. So,
ideally, if you guys want 110%, I would
highly suggest it. It's control and then
move your mouse or you guys go to the
top right, and you guys can do this.
110%, and yeah, I think that's
everything. That's all my settings, my
filters, that's how I trade. Hopefully,
I don't didn't forget anything. But
yeah, also I did forget to mention, if
you guys want to get the wallets I have
tracked, make sure you guys join my
Discord server. It'll also be linked in
the description. If you guys go down, go
ahead to the Discord, you guys will be
spawned into this announcement page.
Make sure you guys verify as well. Make
sure you guys don't connect, don't get
scammed in this server. You guys will
probably get DMs saying, "Yo, I know how
to make money or whatever." Please don't
fall for it. Try to find legitimate
people to trench with, and those people
will probably save your life because I
am now like a Discord server, you know,
FNF, trading with a couple of my
friends. Anyways, forget about all that.
You guys get into this server, scroll
down, you guys will see track wallets.
This is so important because this is how
I find some of my coins, right? If you
guys go here to go to track, you guys
can see live trades. I can see like
Nirox. I can see Nirox, he's made
whatever. I can also pull out the
wallets feed right here. If you guys
click wallets, you guys can click PNL.
But yeah, once again, just go to the
server,
view all file, copy or download it, copy
it, and then go to track, and then go to
wallet manager, import, and then you
just paste it. You just click import.
Just delete this, I believe. Delete this
text, I think. Or just download the file
and copy it and then import it. I just
copied off Discord, and it shows the
extra bit of text. And yeah, now you
guys have wallets to track. Also, I did
forget to mention once again, guys, I
know, just forgive me. If you guys go to
my server, once again, everything is
free. Everything I provide for you is
free. Go to how to start, read this,
bro. Even read this guide.
Make sure you guys go through all of
this, right? I had $0 before I became
profitable, bro. And I literally just
showed up every day, even when I had $0.
I just showed up, trying to understand.
Even if you guys have no money, the
opportunities in this space are so
useful, guys, you know, just showing up
every day, you know? And journal
yourself, take scalps, compound your
portfolios. That's how you guys are
going to grow and win.
Yeah, that's it. Just before the video
starts, guys, I just wanted to make a
quick announcement. I want to thank you
guys for 15,000 subscribers. You know,
subscribing is for free, liking is for
free. I've seen the support I've gotten
in my recent video, and I really thank
you guys. Like, I wouldn't be in this
position without you guys, and I'm just
doing my best to make the best videos
possible, trying to teach you guys,
trying to onboard, trying to teach
people how to make Solana on the Solana
blockchain, trading meme coins. All this
content is for free. I don't have a paid
course, and I do not suggest you guys
buying any paid courses online in the
meme coin space, because it's similarly
how you guys Like, think of it of this
way, right? When you guys are like
solving math equations, you know,
without cheating, going back to the
book, and you try to understand it, then
you genuinely know the knowledge to like
solve the equation in the exam or
whatever. Similarly how in the gym, you
guys are consistent in the gym, you guys
build muscle, you guys are building
brain muscle, you know? You exercising
your brain, and you're trading meme
coins, trying to understand what's going
on. It's how DV started, it's how Cuppsy
started, it's how I started. Especially
with low ports, I would highly suggest
you guys start with low portfolios,
because [music] you have less to lose,
right? Those size, right? Once again, I
do appreciate your support. This
feedback is important for me, because I
understand Oh, you guys like my videos,
you guys don't like my videos. I read
through all the comments, and at the end
of At at end of the video, I will have
me going through Q&A of the comments
just so you guys get a better
understanding, I guess. If you guys
really do care, just watch the video
till the end and I should probably start
doing giveaways, which I will do in my
Discord server hopefully soon. But yeah,
[music] bro, the consistency consistency
part, let me just bring that up again.
Sent it went like I remember Sent it,
right? 2 years ago or what like 1 year
and 1 and 1/2 years ago. He was only
making like 1 or 2 solo a day, but
eventually now he just became the best
trader. Why? Because I know the learning
curve is a bit high now because these
people are putting 15, 16 hours a day
and you guys can do that, too. It's like
even Kimchi. Kimchi was doing 15 hours a
day, he built up his port to like $3
million until Trump came out. I think
more than three. I don't know how much
exactly and he bought $3 million worth
of Trump. He made 15X. He made like 50
mil according to Santos, he made $50
million. Yeah, a lot of people are
tourists in this economy or this space,
but the ones who really stay and
understand and actually [music] believe
in crypto like Solana is only at $76 and
I truly believe there will be another
bull run. There will always be another
bull run, right? You just have to stay
in the space, actually try to learn and
if like in all my 10 years of me trying
to make money online, crypto meme coins
is
>> [music]
>> the place I've made the most money. In
these videos, I probably made over like
$100,000 in all my videos combined just
in my videos. Imagine me trading
offline, you know, without me recording.
So, that's all that's all I wanted to
get out of the way. Hope you guys
enjoyed the video. I tried something new
by trying not like basically just giving
the cons of my Discord call instead of
me voice overing it most of the times.
Anyways, now I want to go over comments.
So, someone asked here, "Why buy vamps
instead of the real?" Basically, vamps
are what make the coin a little bit
better and that's what matters really in
the whole like Solana culture is all
about vamps, I'm not going to lie.
People like it's not fake coins, but
vamping basically let's just say there's
coin A and coin B. Coin A has a spelling
mistake and coin B is a vamp. And that
vamp could be like better coin, you can
say. And they'll just run with that one.
And basically, they just make more
money, like the people that are vamping.
Someone said here, "I have a question.
When someone joins your Discord, do you
DM them and offer them private coaching
or is this a scam?" It's a scam, guys.
Once again, this space has a lot of bad
actors. Please be [music] wary of what
you guys do in the space. Someone asked,
"I'm confused. You are full porting
every trade almost." [music] I am full
porting every trade just because I have
the experience, I know what I'm doing,
and I have risk management, which is
really important. And one thing I do
realize is I tend to round trip a lot,
and this is something I think a lot of
guys will struggle with. But if you guys
take clips on the way up of a coin, you
guys will be good. Here someone said,
"Try to do it new wallets." That's what
I just did today. The first one to 10
soul, I literally proved you don't need
to be tracked to make money. But in the
end, kind of went on my main wallet.
Someone said here, "Interesting. I love
seeing you cool guys farming your
followers, deleting negative comments,
and exploiting them like they are
infinite crops." Guys, have I ever once
farmed you guys? I never deleted a
comment in my life, bro. Your little
trade gambling, right? In my opinion,
[music] right? You guys can see Sent's
P&L, you guys can see Cupsy's P&L. You
guys can see the most consistent
traders' [music] P&L. The ones who show
up every day, they are making money.
It's not really gambling, you know? It's
like [music] How How can you say? It's
like a skill. Like let's say Fortnite,
right? play, win, play, and win. It's
basically like a game, you can say. I
wouldn't say it's gambling. Obviously,
you know, it is like volatile, but
that's what makes meme coins meme coins.
"You seem [music] like a genuine person
ask, I'd like to ask, do you have a stop
loss when trading memes?" Stop loss is,
I think, a mental stop loss. So, I put
it mentally in my head. If anytime I
just don't like the chart, it says like
pattern recognition. That's most of the
times, like if the coin drops a lot, I
just sell. [music] Like 10% 20% loss
mentally. I don't have to like put it on
the chart. I just put it in my head.
Someone asked, "When you're trading to
sell balance, what amount do you put on
prior and [music] what?" So, here's my
slippage. How do I slippage slippage
slippage? Edit presets. [music]
This is my buy settings. This is my sell
settings. And then preset two is this.
And sell settings is this. This is just
cheaper way. [music] For example, if
like I want to lose minimum or like I
can sell anytime I want versus I want
fast exits and fast entries. You know
what I mean? So, these are preset one
and preset two. Those are the only
presets I use. Someone asked, "What
filters you use when trading?" I showed
it in the beginning of the video.
Someone asked, "What extension I use to
fast buy and sell?" It's not an
extension. It's just instant buy. As you
guys can see, instant trade right here.
You can turn it on and off. If you're
starting with one soul, how much should
you be aping? Will you be for for dink?
[music] So, usually if you're starting
with one soul, I believe you should do
.1 buys until you guys are confident
enough and then start increasing your
[music] size. Someone asked the
explanation to not buy OG and wait for
vamp cuz it will probably happen is such
a goldmine. That is unfortunately the
Solana culture. You know, vamps is like
I explained it before, but like it's
just a way for someone to make more
money rather than buying OG. They just
want the floor and make they just make
more money. That's it for today. I hope
you guys enjoyed the video. Subscribe
and like.